eliomotors.com 2013-09-28

# privacy policy - Elio Motors : Elio Motors

Registration information and other personal identifiable information about you that may be collected during your use of the Site is subject to the Elio Motors Privacy Policy, which is incorporated herein by this reference, and can be found at http://www.eliomotors.com/.

This Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) informs you about the ways in which Elio Motors, Inc. (“Elio Motors” “Elio” or “We”) knowingly collects and uses information collected via this {website, www.eliomotors.com (the “Site”).

### Definitions

“Personal Information” means information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

“Non-Personal Information” means information that does not personally identify you and cannot be used to contact you or identify you (for example, your IP Address, your browser type).

“Information” means both Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.

### Information Collected

When we collect Personal Information via the Site, it is only done with your knowledge (such as filling out a submission form). This Personal Information may include your name, email address, telephone number, address, and credit card information.

We also collect and store Non-Personal Information, such as visitor traffic, page hits, site referral information, browser information, downloads, and general Site use information through typical Internet data collection tools, such as web beacons, cookies, and embedded Web links. These tools collect information that your browser sends to our Site, such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the website from which you arrived at this Site, and can track clickstream behavior (i.e. the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take in using the Site). These tools we use do not obtain personal information about you and cannot obtain information from your hard drive or pass on a computer virus. We use this Non-Personal Information to better understand the use of the Site, to improve and revise the Site and to track interest.

Most modern browsers allow users to decide whether to accept cookies, but rejection of cookies may cause some parts of the Site to not function properly or be inaccessible.

Elio Motors also collects Personal and Non-Personal Information from commercially available sources that may be used along with the information Elio Motors collects when you visit the Site. For example, Elio Motors may compare the geographic information acquired from commercial sources with the IP address collected by the data collection tools to derive your general geographic area.

### Use of Information

Elio Motors may use Personal Information, for example, your email address, to provide you with marketing or other communications. Elio Motors may also share your Personal Information with its trusted business partners so they may also offer services that complement those provided by us. We may also share Personal Information and Non Personal Information with third parties that assist us with this Site. For example, we may engage third parties to make improvements on our Site, to offer new products, to provide e-mail and other marketing support, and to allow us to customize your experience on the Site. We also engage another company to validate and process credit card payments. When we engage third To unsubscribe from our mailing list(s), please follow the directions set forth within the promotional or other materials you receive from us or email us at tellmemore@eliomotors.com.

### Linked Internet Web Sites

The Site may include hyperlinks or data that can take you to a third party website, document, file, or other materials. These third party sites will contain their own, different privacy provisions. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting Personal Information to those sites. We are not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these other web sites, and we expressly disclaim any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

### Credit Card Security

Providing you with a secure ordering experience is a high priority. When you submit an order to the Site, we encrypt your order information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software when it is transmitted for credit card processing. Encryption is a process by which software scrambles information in transit. The Site is also registered with site identification authorities to enable your browser to confirm party companies, they have access to Personal Information and Non Personal Information as needed to perform their functions, but they may not use it for other purposes. We do not otherwise disclose any Information to third parties, except if we believe release is necessary to comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order; and to help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect the rights and properties of Elio Motors or its affiliates.

International Customers should note that the database of Personal Information is retained by Elio Motors in the United States. In addition, Personal Information may be shared with a third party to support services for us as described in the paragraph above, and such third party may store Personal Information on servers located in or outside the United States.

Elio Motors identity before any transmission is sent. The identity of our site is automatically confirmed behind the scenes prior to the transmission of any Personal Information requested to complete an online order so that your data reaches your intended target.

When confirming an order to you, we will reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

### Children

Our Site is not directed towards children 13 years of age or under and we do not knowingly collect any information from children 13 years of age or under through the Site.

### Sale of Assets

In the event that there is merger, consolidation, reorganization, or another company acquires the stock or assets of Elio Motors, we reserve the right to include Information among the assets to the changed corporate structure

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Elio Motors may revise this Policy at any time by updating this posting. You should visit this page from time to time to review the current Policy that applies.
